NEHA KUMARI

**Phone No.**: 9599908945

Email ID : neha.nkv1998@gmail.com

To secure a learning position in a reputed organization that offers an excellent opportunity for creativity and professional advancement for self and organizational growth.

# **PROFESSIONAL SYNOPSIS:**

A result oriented **Frontend developer** with Approx. **2.5 years** of qualitative experience in Software industries.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS:**

HTML, CSS, Javascript, React.Js, Redux, Reactstrap, Primereact, materialUi, Git, Bitbucket, SCSS, PSD to HTML, Responsive Web Design

**Tools:-** Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD **Editor:-** Visual studio code, Notepad

Project Management:- Jira,

Basecamp, jenkins

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:**

**Organization:- Oodles Technologies** 

**Duration:** 06 months (May 2021 – present) **Work:** Pando wallet & Explorer, Fabtrack

#### **Description:**

# 1. Pando Wallet & Explorer:-

**Technology used-** Reactis, Redux, javascript, primereact, html, css, bootstrap

- Created Pando wallet and explorer for the brand of pando, using **Reactjs** library.
- Using pando wallet we can send and receive coins and explorer is basically to show the history of all transactions in graphical charts for every token type.
- To create the UI part we have used **primereact**.

#### **Responsibilities:**

- Understand the ongoing project.
- Development of new modules and changes in existing functionalities as per Requirements
- Created the UI part of the apps and functionality as well.
- Coordinated with blockchain team and backend team for apis.

## 2. Fabtrack:-

Technology used- Reactis, Redux, javascript, Reactstrap, html, css

- Fabtrack is a e-commerce website specially for clothing materials.
- Role based project- Admin, seller and buyer along with their teams.
- To create the UI part we have used Reactstrap.

#### **Responsibilities:**

- Created project structure.
- managed two junior frontend developers.
- Development of new modules and changes in existing functionalities as per Requirements

Organization: - Z1 Media

**Duration:** 1 Year (june 2020 – May 2021)

Work: React Dashboard, Ad Products- Engagement unit, Carousel unit

**Team Size:** 6

#### **Description:**

### 3. React is dashboard

- The dashboard is built to show the data of pageviews, mapping, revenue generated along with the creation of units.
- To create the UI part we have used materialUi and sass.

## **Responsibilities:**

- Understand the ongoing project.
- Development of new modules and changes in existing functionalities as per Requirements
- Created the UI part of the whole dashboard.
- Correcting various coding issues, Manual testing and bug fixing

## 4. Ad Products

- Created the UI part of Engagement Unit, as well as the functionality using ES6 or advanced javascript. e.g:- https://a.vdo.ai/core/nd-programmersought-v1/sample
- Created the UI part of Carousel Unit, as well as the functionality using ES6 or advanced javascript.
   e.g:- https://a.vdo.ai/core/c-sample/sample

**Organization: Iconnect ites** 

**Duration:** 1 year (june 2019) to (june 2020)

**Designation:** Jr.Frontend developer

**Projects:** Webpages

Team Size: 4
Description:

### 1. Braunhousehold

- E-commerce website especially for clothing Iron.
- **E.g:** www2.braunhousehold.com

## **Responsibilities:**

- Created the Design using adobe xd
- Worked on development part using HTML, css, javascript, bootstrap, sass, scss
- Correcting various coding issues, Manual testing and bug fixing.

### 2. Delonghi

- E-commerce website especially for coffee machine.
- **E.g:** www.delonghi.com

#### **Responsibilities:**

• Worked on development part using HTML, css, javascript, bootstrap, sass, scss Correcting various coding issues, Manual testing and bug fixing.

# 3. Newconceptplanner

- E-commerce website especially for clothing Iron.
- **E.g:** www.newconceptplanner.com

# **Responsibilities:**

- Created the Design using adobe xd
- Worked on development part using HTML, css, javascript, bootstrap, sass, scss Correcting various coding issues, Manual testing and bug fixing.

# **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND:**

DEGREE	INSTITUTE	UNIVERSITY	YEAR	AGGREGATE %
B.TECH (CSE)	Inderprastha EngineeringCollege	U.P.T.U	2015-2019	72.16
12 <sup>th</sup> (PCMB)	Kendriya vidyalaya	C.B.S.E	2015	78%
10 <sup>th</sup>	Kendriya vidyalaya	C.B.S.E	2013	86%

# **PERSONAL PROFILE:**

Local Address: E-602, Hawelia Valenova Park, Gr. Noida

Father's Name: Balmukund Prasad

**Nationality:** Indian

**Languages:** Hindi and English

I hereby declare that the information given here is correct to my knowledge and I will be responsible for any discrepancy.

Date: Neha kumari